<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Coherent Nonsense</title>
    <link>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Coherent Nonsense</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drifting Forest</title>
      <link>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/drifting-forest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/drifting-forest/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trist</title>
      <link>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/trist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/trist/</guid>
      <description>About Trist is an anonymous social network I used to recreate everytime I learn something new. In this final iteration of Trist, I had discovered the domain driven design architecture, and I went full DDD.
How&amp;rsquo;d It Go? Domain driven design is a pretty nifty idea, but for a small single person project it was a lot of overkill. Creating a feature as simple as logging in had to go through multiple layers of the &amp;lsquo;onion architecture&amp;rsquo; just to return a token.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hyelo</title>
      <link>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/hyelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/hyelo/</guid>
      <description>About I had a phase where I tried making way too many social networks. Somewhere during that period, I wanted to make something very minimal with a couple features that I could implement quickly without the weight of a full social network. I thought an Omegle clone with the addition of private/public chat rooms was a cool idea and so I set myself a weekend to create it.
Tech Stack At the time, I was waist deep in React, though I felt it was a little too much for such a small app (I may have been getting sick of it as well), so I chose to just keep it simple with pure javascript in the front end, and socket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grid Cannon</title>
      <link>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/grid_cannon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://coherentnonsense.github.io/portfolio/projects/grid_cannon/</guid>
      <description>About Inspired by the solitaire game designed by Tom Francis. This is pretty much a filler project until I get more projects. T&amp;rsquo;was a school project that I enjoyed making.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>